Speaker: Valencia – the best city in the world
According to recent surveys, Valencia, in Spain, was voted the best city to live in.
Valencia is situated on the east coast of Spain, about 350 kilometres south of Barcelona.
It is a large city, the third biggest city in Spain after Madrid and Barcelona,
with a population of 837,000 people.
Valencia is famous for its beautiful beaches and also for its historic city centre.
In the old city, there’s a thirteenth-century cathedral,
and many other impressive buildings,
for example, the wonderful central market, and the town hall.
Valencia also has some famous modern buildings designed by architect Santiago Calatrava,
which include the opera house, the science museum, and the aquarium.
It’s also famous for the Fallas celebrations, which take place in March every year.
Come and see why it’s such a good place to visit!